As a, as an existing LP shares
V1 user, when you get to V2,
the first thing you need to do is register.
So you click on the register button and you
see the signup page, then you
need to use your v1 email here.
And you also use your password.
Then you click on the create
account button to get you signed up on v2.
So you'll be sent a verification email.
So you need to confirm your
email and once you confirm it.
You'll be led to the onboarding screen.
So as a migrated user from V1, all your
data will be available on V2 for your profile and
anything you need to update, you can update it.
Or you can change any data
points that is incorrect.
with what you have.
So you can just go through the onboarding.
And update your data as necessary.
Or confirm.
So if everything is correct,
you can just leave it as it is.
And you submit And after onboarding, the
next thing you see is the profile settings.
You can also access the
profile page from here profile.
To confirm that the data is correct
and you can update it if you need to.
Then for the GP profile, so that's for sponsors.
Importantly, you need to claim profile.
You can choose to display sponsor or not,
but you need to.
Claim your profile.
You need to add your linkedin URL as well.
Then you claim your profile to register it on V2,
your GP profile, so.
And for your listings.
So you'll see all your published listings from v1.
You see them here on your listings page on V2.
So you can go through the data to confirm
everything is exactly as you want it to be.
And you can choose, you can choose
to edit it or leave it as it is.
That's up to you.
So some fields are required.
So while going through them you
discover those required fields.
And then you need to update them
if they have not been filled.
And once you're done, you
can just update the deal.
Or if you didn't need to.
Change anything.
You can just close this modal as well.
So all your listings will be available
and you can explore the marketplace.
You can also So when you
create when you have bids.
So you'll find them here on your bids page
for your chats, you communicate with the
listing owner or you request docs.
You'll find them on your chats page.
So yeah, that's the V2 migration guide.
Thank you.